<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<PlayerAbilities>
	<PlayerAbilityGod god="Odin">
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Glass Cannon</name>
			<manacost>1</manacost>
			<description>Odin increases the damage of target unit by 30%, but also increases the damage taken by 30%.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Odin's Blessing</name>
			<manacost>2</manacost>
			<description>Drawing from the powers of the Aesir, Odin blesses all your units, restoring 3 AP for each of them.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Hugin and Munin</name>
			<manacost>15</manacost>
			<description>Hugin and Munin harass target enemy unit, making it regenerate less AP and take 1 damage for 3 turns.</description></PlayerAbility>
	</PlayerAbilityGod>
	<PlayerAbilityGod god="Thor">
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Thunderbolt</name>
			<manacost>1</manacost>
			<description>Thor strikes with the great hammer Mjolnir, summoning a powerful lightning bolt at target unit dealing 8 damage. If the unit is located inwater, all units that stand in nearby water are also struck by lightning.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Comet Strike</name>
			<manacost>6</manacost>
			<description>Thor summons a comet that strikes the target location and destroys any terrain, including impassable terrain such as mountains, replacing it with a crater. Any unit on target tile will take great damage, and area of effect damage is distributed to neighbouring tiles. Cannot target bases or villages.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Thor's Rage</name>
			<manacost>1</manacost>
			<description>Target unit is blessed with Thor's rage and has increased damage</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
	</PlayerAbilityGod>
	<PlayerAbilityGod god="Hel">
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Zombify</name>
			<manacost>40</manacost>
			<description>Hel turns one target enemy unit into a Fallen Warrior under her controll</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Hel's Curse</name>
			<manacost>15</manacost>
			<description>Hel curses target enemy unit with frightening visions. Target unit takes 6 damage each turn until it dies</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Confusion</name>
			<manacost>10</manacost>
			<description>Hel confuses target enemy unit, making it attack itself.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
	</PlayerAbilityGod>
	<PlayerAbilityGod god="Loki">	
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Swap</name>
			<manacost>4</manacost>
			<description>Cunningly, Loki swaps the position of two friendly units.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Freeze</name>
			<manacost>15</manacost>
			<description>Loki freezes target tile. Any unit standing on the tile takes 4 damage and is freezed for 2 turns, meaning it will regenerate less AP each round.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
		<PlayerAbility>
			<name>Uncle Loki Wants You</name>
			<manacost>40</manacost>
			<description>Loki takes control over target enemy unit for 1 round. Also refills target unit's AP.</description>
		</PlayerAbility>
	</PlayerAbilityGod>
</PlayerAbilities>